Grunt work that it can manage too, right?
we've spent months trying to get it to work with the CAD models
and it's just not doing very well.
And I think that's okay because I think plenty of us actually
enjoy doing CAD, you know?
It's very good at image analysis spatial analysis things like
that it's not there yet.
it doesn't live in the 3D world with us it's all just code and
stuff
As far as like the culture, though, like I think there has to
be a balance.
Like we have to use it.
We can't say, hey, we're not going to touch that.
That being said, I'm probably overusing it — probably underusing
it.
You've got to find the balance where you use it, but you understand
how you're using it and what it's doing.